HIKARI KOBE Front-End Developer

(778)840-1785 | Marie h.kobe712@gmail.com | Vancouver, BC | Hikari7 | Portfolio | In hikari-kobe

SUMMARY

A Front-End Developer specialized in React. Keen on building user-friendly websites with my solid knowledge and skills in CSS, JavaScript and React. I have strong communication skills as I have worked a customer service as technical support specialist for 3 years of experience. I am looking to hone my skills as a front-end developer in a team environment.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks, Libraries, and Environments: React, Redux, React Router, Sass, Bootstrap, Material UI, Semantic UI, Styled-component, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Express, Next.js, Gatsby, Node.js

Others: Firebase, MongoDB, Git, Figma

PROJECTS

Workout Tracker (React, Material UI, Firebase)

A workout tracker recording app provides the store the user information and their posts. Manipulating data with Firebase.

Sleep tight (React, GSAP, Tailwind CSS, Youtube Data API v3)

A web app only plays BGM-related relaxing sounds fetched by Youtube Data API. Well designed the minimized styling to help the user to focus on sleeping.

Cook helper (React, Tailwind CSS, Spoonacular API)

A recipe searching app which also provides a grocery list users can add, edit and delete lists.

Oatmeal EC Website (JavaScript (ES6), SASS)

An EC website was made with vanilla JavaScript and used the browser's local storage.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Barista, Starbucks | Vancouver, BC | 2022.8 - Present

• Collaborating with a team of 20 to handle 800 + customers a day.

Technical Support Specialist / Trainer, Japan Concentrix k.k | Japan | 2019.4 - 2022.2

- Offered various customer technical support ranging from supporting the launch of a hotel property's website on the online travel agency site and to game player technical support.
- Trained more than 130 employees successfully and received the Best Employee of the Quarter Award for my training achievements.

EDUCATION

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada | Vancouver, BC | 2022.5 - Present

- Web and Mobile Application Development Diploma
- Learned core skills related to a front-end developer: JavaScript(ES6), ReactJS, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, BootStrap, Git, etc...

Seinan Gakuin University | Japan | 2014.4 - 2018.3

· Bachelor of Intercultural studies